## Pak Hong (James) Leung

Github – <a href="https://github.com/james-leung">https://github.com/james-leung</a> Website – <a href="https://james-leung.github.io">https://james-leung.github.io</a> Email – <a href="mailto:jifly12@gmail.com">jlfly12@gmail.com</a>

## Full-stack Web Developer

As someone with a Ph.D. in physics, I am a natural problem-solver with extensive experience in leading teams of researchers, mentoring junior students, and writing peer-reviewed scientific papers. With 5+ years of experience in object-oriented programming, I am now an aspiring web developer, with a focus on building responsive single-page applications (SPA) using Angular as well as robust and efficient REST APIs using .Net Core 3.1 and Node.js. I have also taken an interest in solving algorithms, having completed 100+ questions on LeetCode with Javascript.

## Technical Skill Set

Frameworks	Languages	Source Control	Other Skills
<ul><li>.Net Core</li></ul>	• C#	<ul><li>Git</li></ul>	<ul> <li>HTML / CSS</li> </ul>
EF Core	<ul> <li>Typescript</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Azure Devops</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>SOLID Principles</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Node.js &amp; Express</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Javascript</li> </ul>		<ul> <li>SQL Databases</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Angular 2+ &amp; React</li> </ul>	<ul><li>Python</li></ul>		<ul> <li>Visual Studio</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Bootstrap 4</li> </ul>			

# **Projects**

- Burgler Fast food ordering website (.Net Core, Angular, SQL Server): <a href="https://burgler.azurewebsites.net/">https://burgler.azurewebsites.net/</a>
- My portfolio website (Jekyll): https://james-leung.github.io/
- Quantum Circuit Simulator (Python)
   <a href="https://github.com/james-leung/Quantum-circuit-simulator/">https://github.com/james-leung/Quantum-circuit-simulator/</a>
- An optimiser for 2-qubit quantum gates (Python)

## **Professional Experience**

#### Individual Software Developer

2018 - now

- Front-end: using Angular 2+ to build client-side SPA applications handling JSON data
- Back-end: using .Net Core 3.1+ to build REST-ful API's that are secure and robust

- Established CI / CD pipelines using Azure DevOps with complete deployment cycles
- Writing unit tests (e.g. XUnit) to make sure the application behaves as intended
- Completed dozens of Udemy courses on full-stack web development and programming best practices
- Solved LeetCode algorithms of all difficulties with Javascript

# **Duke University Graduate Student Programmer**

2018 - 2020

It was my responsibility to simulate quantum circuit operations in a system of trapped ions, where I established the link between error parameters and output circuit parameters.

- Wrote my own quantum circuit simulator (90 % agreement between simulation and experiment)
- Coding Python in Jupyter Notebook
- Worked with teams of up to 5 people (quantum control group)
- Weekly presentations using whiteboard and projector

### Georgia Institute of Technology Graduate Teaching Assistant

2015 - 2017

Nurturing undergraduate students in physics in interactive labs and Q&A sessions.

- Briefing students in physics labs using whiteboard (class sizes of about 30)
- Teaching students Python code using the IDLE IDE
- Help desks: 1-to-many and 1-to-1 tutorials where I helped students with their assignments and exams
- Grading mid-term exams according to a marking scheme

## **Education and Training**

#### **Education:**

**2018-2020** Duke University: Ph.D. in physics

2015-2017 Georgia Institute of Technology: Master's in physics2011-2015 Chinese University of Hong Kong: Bachelor's in physics

Please contact me for references.